hello welcome back today i'm sharing
with you a 30 second french twist hair
tutorial now this is an updated faster
easier version of my previous french
twist which now has over 4.3 million
views and is my most viewed video on my
entire channel thank you but let's keep
this short and sweet and let's get
started to help create texture and
volume you can add some volumizing
powder to your roots at the crown and
just brush it through next toss all your
hair back and gather it into a low
ponytail and my side sections swoop over
my ears but feel free to make yours
tight and sleek then go ahead and gently
pull up the hair at your crown to add
some volume and of course pull out your
face framing pieces all right french
twist time so hold your ponytail in your
right hand and take your index and
middle finger on your left hand and
tightly wrap the base of your ponytail
up and over your fingers to the right
next hook and tightly twist your fingers
to the left twisting one full turn
counterclockwise as you bring it to the
top of your head using your right hand
to keep your ends at the bottom now hold
your twist tightly in place against your
head and with your right hand gently
pull up the base of your twist upwards
to create that french twist look now as
you pull you can tuck your hair
underneath your twist to keep everything
nice and tight and don't forget to tuck
your ends oh and feel free to tuck it in
at the top but i like mine higher so
that you can see it from the front all
right hold your twist tightly against
your head with one hand and to secure i
highly recommend using french pins they
hold the hair so well and i like to bend
mine so they fit more comfortably now
start at the bottom hook it through the
outside of your twist to the right then
push it against your head and in towards
the middle and then keep repeating this
technique up your twist and i probably
used about five to six pins and it feels
very secure and don't forget to pin the
top of your twist as well especially if
you kept it larger like i did and there
you have it a very simple yet elegant
french twist hairstyle but thank you so
much for watching and if you liked
today's video please give it a thumbs up
subscribe and i'll talk to you next time
bye